A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Affairs Division, Program Staff Files FA548
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International Training Evaluation, 1969-1983; IV
  - Grant File -- Background Reports on Africa Training Project, Eastern Africa Universities Research Project Policy Conference, USAID/Indonesia Training Project Evaluation, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Grant File -- "Evaluating the Effects of Ford Foundation Support for Education Abroad of Third World Nationals, 1960-1980: A Pre-Proposal," Outline, Notes, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Grant File -- "Evaluating the Effects of Ford Foundation Support for Education Abroad of Third World Nationals, 1960-1980: A Project Description," Progress Report, Jul-Dec 1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Grant File -- Memoranda Re: Proposal to Evaluate International Division Support for Training, Preliminary Outline for Final Report, Notes, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Grant File -- References -- Bibliography of Mimeos, Books, etc., [1983] (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Grant File -- Training Study Interview Notes, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - India -- Background on FF Support for Graduate Fellowships for Indian Government Officers at Harvard and Williams College, [1960s-1970s] (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE) -- Memoranda, Correspondence, Outline for Evaluation Study of Foreign Educational Experiences by Elinor Barber, 1978-1982 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Inter-American Foundation -- Background and Evaluation Report on Doctoral Fellowship Program, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - International Development Research Centre (IDRC) -- Correspondence, Evaluation Report on IDRC Fellowship Program, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Latin American Scholarship Program of American Universities (LASPAU) -- Alumni Survey, List of 1977 Active Scholars (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - OLAC (Office for Latin America & the Caribbean) Education Program -- Memoranda Re: Report on Training of Nationals in Educational Planning, Budget Projections for Education, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - OLAC Graduate Fellowship Program -- Memoranda, Annual Reports (1 of 2), 1969-1978 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - OLAC Graduate Fellowship Program -- Memoranda, Annual Reports (2 of 2), 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - OLAC Human Resources Training Inventory -- Data for Brazil, Argentina, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - OLAC Human Resources Training Inventory -- Data for Chile, Mexico, Peru, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - OLAC Human Resources Training Inventory -- Data for Colombia, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - OLAC Human Resources Training Inventory for Education, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Questionnaire -- Evaluation Questionnaires Used by AID, African-American Institute, Rockefeller Foundation, and IIE, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Questionnaire -- FF Questionnaire to Peruvian Study Abroad Alumni, Notes, Draft Questionnaires, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Reproductive Biology -- "Directory of Ford Foundation Fellows in Reproductive Biology, 1960-1972", 1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Third Country Training -- Memoranda Re: Requests for Information on Training Institutions Abroad, Papers, Notes on FF Cases by Country, etc., 1975-1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Turkey -- Evaluation of FF Science Education Program in Turkey, 1960-1980, Sep 1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Working File -- Conclusions -- Summary Conclusion Drafts, Comments, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Working File -- Methodology -- Notes on Strategies, Evaluation Outline, Field Office Contacts, Grants by Country, etc., 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - World Bank -- Background and Notes on Economic Development Institute (EDI) Courses and Evaluation, 1975-1982 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Program Planning Budgets, 1962-1983; V
  This series consists of program planning budgets (also called proposed budget books) for the fiscal years 1963-1985 kept by the International Division. The budgets from 1962 through 1970 contain overviews of program work and goals, as well as projected budget allocations for the International Division and International Affairs. Beginning in 1970, the Foundation combined the annual planning budgets for the various program divisions into one report.
  - International Affairs Program: Planning Budget Request for Fiscal 1963-1964-1965, Sep 1962 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - International Affairs Program: Planning Budget Request for Fiscal 1964-1965-1966, Jun 1963 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - International Affairs Program: Planning Budget Request for Fiscal 1965-1966-1967, Jun 1964 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - International Affairs Program: Planning Budget Request for Fiscal 1966-1967-1968, Jun 1965 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - International Affairs Program: Planning Budget Request for Fiscal 1967-1968-1969, Jun 1966 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - International Division: Program Budget Request Fiscal Year 1968, Jun 1967 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - International Division: Program Budget Fiscal Year 1969, Jun 1968 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - International Division: Proposed Budget Fiscal Year 1970 (1of 2), Jun 1969 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - International Division: Proposed Budget Fiscal Year 1970 (2 of 2), Jun 1969 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Proposed Budget Fiscal Year 1970: Summary, Jun 1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Proposed Budget Fiscal Year 1971 (1 of 2), Jun 1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Proposed Budget Fiscal Year 1971 (2 of 2), Jun 1970 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Proposed Budget Fiscal Year 1972, Jun 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Proposed Budget Fiscal Year 1973, Jun 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Budget Fiscal Years 1974 and 1975, Jun 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Revisions in 1975 Program Budget and Preliminary Presentations of 2-Year Program Budgets for FY 1976 and 1977, Mar 1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Proposed Budget Fiscal Years 1976 and 1977, Jun 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - FY 1978-FY 1979 Budget Planning: Program Alternatives and Options, Mar 1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Proposed Budget Fiscal Years 1978 and 1979, Jun 1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - A Program Budget Planning Paper for FY 1980 & FY 1981 (by McGeorge Bundy), Mar 1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Proposed Program Budget Fiscal Years 1980 and 1981, Jun 1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Proposed Program Budget Fiscal Years 1982 and 1983, Jun 1981 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Proposed Budget for Fiscal Years 1984-85, Jun 1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)